all right but Acquia hello hello
可以，但是Acquia你好
okay that's right so welcome to talk
好的，没错，欢迎谈谈
about java.util concurrent flow what was
关于java.util并发流是什么
previously known as reactive streams and
以前称为反应流和
it's gonna be above a quick look back at
快速浏览一下
what it actually I made a coin or just
实际上我做了一个硬币还是
to me okay so it's just me if it's yours
对我好吧，如果是你，那就是我
echo okay so say Friday so my name is
回声好吧，所以说星期五，所以我的名字是
Carmen offski I work at light wind so
卡门·斯基斯基我在微风中工作，所以
company behind Scala play a go on
Scala背后的公司继续前进
distributed micro services and basically
分布式微服务，基本上
it's called programming language as well
它也被称为编程语言
but all of our API eyes have a Java API
但是我们所有的API眼睛都有Java API
which I'll talk about a bit but not too
我会谈一点，但不会太过
much and I also did reactive streams TCK
很多，我也做了反应流TCK
so you'll see what reactive streams
所以你会看到什么反应流
actually is it's not something you can
其实这不是你可以做的
pick up and use it's more of a just a
拿起并使用它只是一个
standard and we'll talk about why would
标准，我们将讨论为什么
you care about a standard like that and
您关心的是这样的标准，
how it actually came to be other than
它实际上是如何变得不同于
that I do a lot of community stuff in
我在其中做了很多社区工作
Poland like geek on conference like 1200
波兰像极客一样参加1200会议
people each year reports Java is a group
每年都有人报告Java是一个小组
I found it was carly was a group like
我发现这很像卡里
white paper reading clubs things like
白皮书阅读俱乐部之类的东西
that anyway so the usual question on
无论如何，所以通常的问题
conferences who is not heard of archive
没有听说过存档的会议
I cans up and I won't be offended
我罐起来，我不会被冒犯
okay who has heard and maybe even used
好，谁听说过甚至使用过
it
它
oh cool okay so people lost questions so
哦，好吧，所以人们输了问题，所以
who has heard about reactive streams
谁听说过反应流
okay so you know about react issues so
好吧，所以你知道有关反应的问题，所以
we'll see how much we can skip or how
我们将看到我们可以跳过多少或如何
much not but occurs a bit more than what
不多，但比发生的更多
we do and distributed computing yeah by
我们做和分布式计算是的
the way we have the ARCA streams
我们拥有ARCA流的方式
implementation which is a reactive
实施是被动的
streams implementation yourself an HTTP
通过HTTP自己实现实现
to server and of course distributed
到服务器，当然是分布式的
cluster so brief reminder for people who
如此简短的提醒人群
don't know what a car is that's a number
不知道那是什么车
of the tools we have in the tool set
工具集中有哪些工具
and we're pretty much pick and choose if
我们几乎可以选择是否
you just want to use our Parker we're
您只想使用我们的Parker
talking about our Parker to Dave it's
谈论我们的派克戴夫
like an integrations thing also
像整合的东西
streaming right which is why it fits
流权，这就是为什么它适合
into today's topic you can just pick
进入今天的话题，您可以选择
that you don't need to do the actress or
不需要做演员或
clustering and vice versa so basically
集群，反之亦然
end of corporate pitch let's talk tech
企业宣传的结束让我们来谈谈技术
so stream is probably one of the most
所以流可能是最
overloaded terms right now everything is
现在重载条款
streaming even if it isn't streaming
即使没有流媒体
people call it streaming good example
人们称它为流媒体很好的例子
would be spark streaming which is kind
将是火花流这是一种
of streaming quote-unquote but
流引用-取消引用但
practically speaking it's more
实际上说的更多
mini-batches and you get very different
迷你批次，您会变得与众不同
semantics between all of the different
所有不同语言之间的语义
libraries which claimed that their
声称他们的图书馆
streaming libraries you get for more
流媒体库，您可以获得更多
dictate oriented things like spark
决定诸如火花之类的导向性事物
flaying whatnot and then you get things
虚张声势然后你得到东西
like reactor streams which is more on
像反应堆流一样
the level of like an input stream right
像输入流一样的水平
sometimes people ask me to compare
有时人们要我比较
reactive streams with I don't know spark
我不知道火花的反应流
streaming right that question doesn't
正确播放该问题
really make that much sense because how
真的很有意义，因为
would you compare back in the old days
你会比较过去吗
compare Hadoop to input stream right not
比较Hadoop输入流不正确
not quite the same thing
不太一样
even though okay both have similar
即使两个都差不多
concept thing goes anything goes out so
概念的东西什么都消失了，所以
this is a bit of terminology and then
这是一些术语，然后
we'll jump back into the past to see
我们将跳回过去看看
where it all came from so this is
一切都来自哪里，所以这是
archive strange terminology we call
存档奇怪的术语，我们称之为
things a bit more specifically than some
事情比一些更具体
other libraries on the same level so an
同一级别的其他库
example would be our X Java for example
例如我们的X Java
value talk about observable and
谈论可观察的价值和
everything is an observable and our
一切都是可观察的，我们
streams we have source flow sink and it
流，我们有源流沉，它
depends how many inputs and how many
取决于多少输入和多少
outputs it has so it's a bit more in
输出，所以有更多
your face but this is for consuming data
你的脸，但这是为了消耗数据
or this is for transforming data etc and
或者这是用于转换数据等
we have a synchronous boundaries and
我们有一个同步的边界，
visas were reactive streams is actually
签证实际上是反应性的
a meaning for a new school and what
新学校的意义以及什么
we'll talk about today so they're
我们今天要谈的是
synchronous boundaries between these
这些之间的同步边界
processing elements each of those could
处理元素，每个都可以
be actually
实际上
different technology so it doesn't have
不同的技术，所以它没有
to be our constraints and backpressure
成为我们的约束和背压
service for two main features of
服务的两个主要特点
reactive streams it does flow control so
反应流，它确实进行流量控制，因此
it prevents out the memory errors like
它可以防止内存错误，例如
that and it's a standard so multiple
那是一个很多种的标准
libraries can interrupt between each
库之间可以中断
other but I want to fast forward a bit
其他，但我想快一点
and talk about the second most
再说第二
overloaded word on the planet right now
现在地球上的重载单词
which is reactive to West Point
对西点有反应
overloaded that I wrote a mini book to
我写了一本迷你书给
kind of clarify what reactive really is
澄清什么才是真正的反应性
and it's not just reactive streams which
不仅是反应流
many people would want you to believe
很多人会希望你相信
right now it's a bit more than that
现在不止于此
if you remember the reactive manifesto
如果你还记得反应式宣言
years ago that's at least how we think
至少那是我们的想法
about it why we mean well akka people
关于它，为什么我们说好的客家人
right meant people we think it's a bit
正确意味着我们认为这有点
bigger than just reactive programming so
不仅仅是反应式编程，所以
forever peacetime Oryx Java akka stream
永远和平时期的Oryx Java akka流
style it's a nice building block but
样式，这是一个不错的构建块，但是
that's not my entire story it won't help
那不是我的全部故事，这无济于事
you achieve end goal that we had in mind
您实现了我们所想到的最终目标
to an victor kind of initiated a very
胜利者发起了一个非常
active streams thing okay so reactive
活跃的流事物还可以，所以反应灵敏
apps awesome absolutely topic of today's
应用程序绝对是当今的主题
talk not vampire thing so there's more
不说吸血鬼的事情，所以还有更多
stuff to that like and things like
诸如此类的东西
resiliency and being able to scale out
弹性并能够横向扩展
or down that's also part of reactive
或下降，这也是反应的一部分
systems at least how we defined it back
系统至少我们如何定义它
fan and very active manifesto so why did
粉丝和非常活跃的宣言，为什么
we actually set out to do reactive
我们实际上着手进行反应
stream so people here have raised their
流，所以这里的人们提高了他们的
hands but they know attractive streams
手，但他们知道吸引人的溪流
was and this but why did it actually
曾经是，但这是为什么呢
come into our minds that we need this
进入我们的想法
thing so basically in my team we would
基本上在我们团队中，我们会
have a lot of customers that come in to
有很多顾客进来
us and basically would be a project
我们，基本上是一个项目
rewrite or a greenfield and they want to
重写还是未开发的，他们想要
use some reactive technology they pick a
使用一些反应技术，他们选择了
curve they rewrite the system or they
曲线他们重写系统，或者他们
write a new system and it's super
编写一个新系统，它超级好
awesome
很棒
Andres traffic like a boss great cursing
安德烈斯的交通像老板一样大骂人
on sunglasses everyone everyone's happy
戴墨镜的每个人都很高兴
they put it for load testing
他们把它用于负载测试
everything's fine
一切安好
they put it in production
他们把它投入生产
integrates with other systems and for
与其他系统集成
other systems
其他系统
what have ever not been modernized or
尚未现代化的东西
just or even not under your control it
只是或什至不在您的控制之下
could be a third party or something and
可能是第三方等
some of them don't really handle that
他们中的一些人并不能真正解决这个问题
new traffic you slam at them and it ends
你猛烈抨击他们的新交通就结束了
up like that so it was really driven by
像这样，所以它真的是由
a need but ok on one hand it's great for
有需要但一方面还可以
the our APIs so fast and what we can
我们的API这么快，我们可以
claim to people ha look at our car so
声称对人们哈看我们的车所以
fast so great
速度真快
on the other hand we want to integrate
另一方面，我们要整合
nicely with the rest of the planet right
与地球其他地方很好
we don't want to keep crushing the rest
我们不想继续粉碎其余的
of your company by overloading them just
通过使他们超载而使公司
because we can process things first
因为我们可以先处理事情
revenge some other system so that's the
报仇其他系统，这就是
prime need for flow control etc
流量控制等的主要需求
specifically an asynchronous programming
特别是异步编程
so rocket rocket is all about a
所以火箭火箭就是关于
synchronous programming just adding flow
同步编程只是增加流程
control to the thing isn't as trivial as
对事物的控制不如对事物的琐碎
it is in a blocking application because
它在阻止应用程序中，因为
in a blocking application you're
在阻止应用程序中
basically automatically being slowed
基本上会自动变慢
down because you're blocking until
下来，因为你一直阻塞到
someone has processed right right and on
有人正确地处理了
synchronous app you kind of can keep
您可以保留的同步应用程序
going and keep going even while the
继续前进，即使
thing is not done processing on the
事情还没有完成处理
other side so this is the kind of
另一面，这是那种
immediate need that we wanted to address
我们想要解决的迫切需求
with three years ago or something
三年前
nowadays was a funny pattern that we see
如今，我们看到了一个有趣的模式
from people I would just slap a calf can
我会拍一小腿罐
vary a little bit it would be solved
稍有不同将解决
right and I found that very funny
对，我发现这很有趣
because an offer I think those two
因为我认为这两个要约
offers in that book and he tweeted that
那本书中的要约，他在推特上说
one issue that keeps coming up with
一个不断提出的问题
Kafka Connect so that's that's the kind
Kafka Connect，那就是那种
of system where you wanna like drain
您想流失的系统
from a database into Kafka or the
从数据库导入Kafka或
opposite many downstream systems don't
相反，许多下游系统没有
scale as well as comfortable it sounds
听起来既规模又舒适
familiar right
熟悉的权利
same story new tech faster than other
同一故事的新技术比其他新技术快
systems other systems still valuable
其他系统仍然有价值的系统
maybe probably even making money your
也许甚至可以赚钱
system not even net making money because
系统甚至没有净赚钱，因为
another production so you know it's a
另一个作品，所以你知道这是一个
bit hard to argue and if
有点难辩，如果
you would be away and here I'm hinting
你会离开，在这里我暗示
it for a pocket project which you will
它是一个口袋项目，你会
see what it's all about it's basically
基本上了解它的全部内容
about integrating these various
关于整合这些各种
technologies without having to lock you
技术而不必锁定您
in or be very specific about oh yeah we
或非常具体哦，是的，我们
only like these technologies we don't
只喜欢这些技术，我们不
like that technology's kind of like
就像那种技术
camera but we'll get tipped so this is
相机，但我们会给您打底，所以这是
the immediate need we kind of wanted to
我们想要的迫切需求
address react extreme starts three or so
地址反应极端开始三个左右
years ago so the reason I talk about
多年前，所以我谈论的原因
this stuff and you see me talking about
这些东西，你看到我在谈论
it so it did for TCK ever so of a set of
它为TCK做过一系列
tests would verify if you actually
测试会验证您是否确实
implemented it correctly and you'll see
正确实施它，您会看到
why that actually matters because
为什么这实际上很重要，因为
nowadays it's part of JDK 9 and that
如今，它已成为JDK 9的一部分，
super core were super excited about it
超级核心对此感到非常兴奋
it was included violent ugly and for jab
它包括暴力丑陋和刺戳
266 so the more concurrency updates lots
266所以更多的并发更新了很多
of very interesting things here but one
这里非常有趣的事情之一
of them being reactive streams basically
他们基本上是反应流
copy pasted and renamed to each other
复制粘贴并彼此重命名
concurrent flow but all of the semantics
并发流，但所有语义
and rules about how we behave are
关于我们的行为的规则是
versing remember that that's kind of
记住，那是一种
important point so it's exactly reactive
重要的一点，所以它是完全反应的
streams but okay it's not for exact
流，但是好吧，这不是确切的
types so now we'll have to have some
类型，所以现在我们必须有一些
period of time where libraries will have
图书馆将拥有的时间段
to support both what because we wanted
支持这两个，因为我们想要
to build an ecosystem kind of prove to
建立一种生态系统来证明
Doug and what if a Java ecosystem that
Doug，如果Java生态系统
okay this is valuable and now we have to
好的，这很有价值，现在我们必须
kind of port all of this to the flow
有点把所有这些都带到流
interface should be pretty easy so if
界面应该很简单，所以如果
you're curious about can you already
你很好奇你已经可以了
today use the flow interface and the
今天使用流接口和
great things absolutely and we support
绝对是伟大的事情，我们支持
that already Annika we just released a
Annika已经发布了
jar of it can integrate with flow
它的罐子可以与流整合
interface and at the same time you can
界面，同时您可以
still integrate with reactive streams
仍与反应流集成
interfaces so technically it's a
接口，从技术上讲，这是一个
breaking change because package rename
重大更改，因为包重命名
but practically you won't feel any pain
但实际上您不会感到任何痛苦
from that so so it's more of an SPI and
因此，它更像是SPI，
by which I mean to say that it's
我的意思是说
integration thing
整合的东西
right you have these various
对，你有这些各种
technologies and when we did work the
技术以及我们工作时
streams we invited the spring peepers or
溪流我们邀请了春季偷窥者或
project reactor world's great people
工程反应堆世界的伟大人物
that's a bit says : ecosystem specific
有点说：特定于生态系统
the arocs Java project of course with
当然是arocs Java项目
Ben Christiansen was on board from the
本·克里斯蒂安森（Ben Christiansen）从
very beginning from Red Hat we had
从红帽开始
vertex and all these different vendors
顶点和所有这些不同的供应商
but kind of solve the same problem and
但是可以解决相同的问题，
we decided okay let's band together
我们决定好吧，让我们在一起
build this thing and then we'll all
建立这个东西，然后我们都会
benefit instead of having everybody to
受益而不是让所有人
look into very eco system let's build a
研究非常生态的系统，让我们建立一个
bigger ecosystems it's going to be
更大的生态系统
beneficial to everyone so I think I'll
对所有人都有利，所以我想
fast forward a bit River history here
在这里快进一点河的历史
but like I said 2014 we had kind of
但就像我说的2014年，
three parts to it play sober play
三个部分起到清醒作用
framework had introduced and back
框架已经介绍并返回
pressured API in play called the
使用中的压力API称为
treaties back then it was you were
当时的条约是
thinking okay maybe that's gonna solve
觉得好吧，也许那会解决
it practically speaking it was way way
实际上就是这样
too complex for end-users to be mice
对于最终用户来说太复杂了
nice to use we had a nice iolair but
很好用我们有一个很好的iolair但是
none of these api's were a nice API to
这些api都不是一个很好的API
work with so at the bank Christensen
在克里斯坦森银行（Christensen）与之合作
brought to the table was with Oryx Java
带到桌子上的是Oryx Java
a nice API to work with around which we
一个很好的API，可以与我们一起使用
built on the concept of back pressure
建立在背压的概念上
which Oryx Java didn't initially have
Oryx Java最初没有的
then we added it's kind of during this
然后我们添加了某种
work together on it anyway so that's for
无论如何都要一起工作，这是为了
at ease if you quickly look at it you
放心，如果您快速看一下，您
can kind of imagine it doesn't speak to
可以想象它没有说话
you in five seconds what it actually
你在五秒钟之内
does so that's why we scraped that it
这样做是为什么我们将其刮掉了
would solve the problem of flow control
会解决流量控制的问题
and back pressure but it was very husky
和背压，但非常沙哑
inspired and didn't quite feel as native
受到启发并且不太像本土人
to to Java as corner developers so we
以Java作为角落开发人员，所以我们
sacked that and when this interaction
以及当这种互动时解雇
began of kind of nailing down what we're
开始确定我们的目标
gonna solve talked about that already
要解决已经谈论过
and then finally it gets included in
最后，它包含在其中
okay right so what does that leave us
好的，那那给我们留下了什么
it leaves us with these interfaces
这些接口给了我们
currently in the JDK that you can use
目前在您可以使用的JDK中
right now
马上
but I'll ask you to not implement them
但我会要求您不要实施
directly because when you look at them
直接因为当你看着他们
it's basically seven methods or so for
这基本上是七种方法
interfaces looks very simple but as any
界面看起来非常简单，但是
concurrency thing it's it has a lot of
并发的事情是它有很多
implications when and how you can invoke
何时和如何调用的含义
things right so that's the actual
正确的事情，这是实际的
complexity of react extremes that's per
极端反应的复杂性
spec I can zoom in on some random rule
我可以放大一些随机规则
and let's try to see mm that's not
让我们尝试看看这不是
interesting not for example as a problem
有趣的不是作为一个问题
must be prepared to receive a non
必须准备接受非
complete signal with or without
有或没有信号完整
proceeding requests core so we can
处理请求核心，以便我们可以
complete with an empty string for
用一个空字符串完成
example right seems obvious but if
正确的例子似乎很明显，但是如果
you're kind of implementation assumes
你是一种实现假设
ofs always going to be a request before
以前总是要提出要求
a complete signal well you would be
一个完整的信号，你会
wrong
错误
so rather than implementing it directly
因此，而不是直接实施
I'd recommend using an existing library
我建议使用现有的库
can be our customs can be any of our
可以是我们的习俗可以是我们的任何一个
implementations the JDK ships with one
JDK附带的实现
example published wrong it's not very
例子发布错了不是很好
powerful but you can get started with it
功能强大，但您可以开始使用它
so let's explain reactive streams in a
因此，让我们解释一下
single slide the protocol is actually
单张幻灯片实际上是协议
not very difficult and we settled on the
不是很困难，我们选择了
naming publisher and subscriber was a
命名发布者和订阅者是一个
big naming debate back then so it's not
那时的大命名辩论不是
pops up that's kind of my problem with a
弹出来是我的问题
current names of it when you say publish
您说发布时的当前名称
or subscriber people think pops up right
或订阅者认为弹出框正确
make sense but it's specifically a
很有道理，但这特别是
point-to-point protocol right you can't
点对点协议
do a fan-out thing using this protocol
使用此协议进行扇出操作
but when each interaction is going to be
但是当每次互动都会
adhering to this kind of rules how to
遵守这种规则
interact it it's not defined on the set
互动它没有在集合上定义
of subscribers it's on a point-to-point
的订户是点对点的
basis so since we aimed to solve flow
基础，因为我们旨在解决流程
control mechanism here
这里的控制机制
and it's obviously gonna be a
而且显然是
synchronous with the purpose of it so
与它的目的同步
usually you do have some kind of buffer
通常你有某种缓冲
in your system that's drawn here as this
在您的系统中绘制如下
smaller shape and you're processing some
较小的形状，您正在处理一些
messages what's going on a synchronously
消息同步发生了什么
you have something's buffered still and
您仍然缓冲着某些东西，
you have some free space in your buffer
您的缓冲区中有一些可用空间
if you think you don't have a buffer you
如果您认为自己没有缓冲，
have a buffer somewhere anyway because
无论如何在某处有缓冲，因为
either it's gonna be network or i/o or
要么是网络，要么是I / O，要么
something somewhere we'll have some
在某个地方我们会有一些
buffer space and then a synchronous
缓冲空间，然后同步
system so let's say we define that we
系统，假设我们定义了
talk about elements so unlike TCP we
谈论元素，所以与TCP不同，我们
don't talk about okay give me this many
不要谈论好吧，给我这么多
bytes from this infinite stream of blob
来自此无限blob流的字节
data we talk about specific elements so
我们谈论特定元素的数据
it could be person might give me one
可能有人会给我一个
person give me three persons so here a
一个人给我三个人，所以这里一个
green arrow says I'm requesting three
绿色箭头表示我要三个
elements which also can be said as I am
我也可以说的元素
prepared to accept at most three
准备最多接受三个
elements right because you kind of know
正确的元素，因为您知道
your buffer space you see okay if you
您的缓冲区空间，如果您认为可以，
give me three elements I will not blow
给我三个要素，我不会吹
up and upstream so the publisher even
上游和上游，因此发布商甚至
though it can be faster it can never
虽然它可以更快，但永远不会
signal more elements than it was
发出更多的信号
confirmed asked for now this basically
确认现在基本要求
and a rule that requests kind of add up
和要求加总的规则
but basically solve a simple flow
但基本上解决了一个简单的流程
control problem with some edge cases
一些边缘情况下的控制问题
around completion and cancellation error
围绕完成和取消错误
handling but that's why we have this
处理，但这就是为什么我们有这个
back and TCK so like I said ships are
回来和TCK，就像我说的
not already so you don't have to wait to
还没有，所以您不必等待
adopt it pretty happy that we were able
很高兴我们能够
to prove it off didn't really need multi
证明它并不需要多
release jars to that if someone's
如果有人
thinking about how do people adopt his
考虑人们如何接受他的
thing for introducing new API motorist
介绍新的API驾驶者的事情
jars are not that helpful
罐子不是那么有用
we're hopeful for changing
我们希望改变
implementation
实作
for example if we had using had been
例如，如果我们曾经使用过
using some unsafe features now we can
现在使用一些不安全的功能，我们可以
move on to other alternatives like VAR
继续使用其他替代方法，例如VAR
hand drives etc but for introducing new
手动驱动器等，但用于引入新驱动器
API if you produce libraries or if you
API（如果您产生库或如果您
consume libraries that's not the tool
使用不是工具的库
that helps you out with that
可以帮助您
specifically so it's just a normal job
特别是，这只是正常工作
that was linked to us JDK 9 class so
链接到我们的JDK 9类，所以
intro up in action doesn't actually work
实际上进行介绍并不起作用
just a quick example that across a
只是一个简单的例子
number of implementations just works
可行的实现数量
it's kind of boring to demo these things
演示这些东西有点无聊
and show these things because just works
并展示这些东西，因为它是可行的
but that's a feature so a bit more arca
但这是一个功能，所以更多
streams so we had a brief look at kind
流，所以我们简要地看了一下
of diagrams but let's look at code and
图，但让我们看一下代码和
they used Java here some of the slides
他们在这里使用Java
will be Scala but your notice with API
将是Scala，但您使用API​​的通知
saw very very similar especially with
看到非常非常相似，尤其是
the lambda and lambda support since Java
自Java以来​​的lambda和lambda支持
8 it's getting more and more similar so
8它越来越相似
pretty happy about that as you can see
如您所见，对此感到非常高兴
we have syncs flows so flow is like a
我们有同步流程，所以流程就像一个
function basically and if you're curious
基本起作用，如果您好奇
about why do we have free type
关于为什么我们有自由类型
parameters here in the flow and to in a
流程中的参数以及
source that's basically because we found
来源基本上是因为我们发现
that very often you need to interact oK
很多时候你需要互动
we've invested REME it's easy right you
我们已经投资了REME，您很容易
do a stream processing operations you
做一个流处理操作
forward you reduce you you matter but
转发你减少你的事情，但
very often you need to either inject
很多时候您需要注入
some control from the outside world or
来自外界的一些控制或
some observability like a like a
一些像
god-like are like a rate meter or like a
像上帝一样，就像一个速率表或一个
fraud ler that you want to control from
您想控制的欺诈者
the outside so we have that in a type
外面，所以我们有一个类型
safe fashion but each stage can produce
安全时尚，但每个阶段都能产生
some kind of value that has been typed
已经输入的某种价值
you have it in your hand and you can do
你手里拿着它，你可以做
stuff to it and we have a special type a
东西，我们有一个特殊的类型
type called not used but you can more
类型称为未使用，但您可以更多
nicely expressed that okay I'm not using
很好地表达了，我没有使用
this type parameter rather than sticking
这种类型的参数，而不是坚持
void everywhere
到处都是空的
this was something that we didn't like
这是我们不喜欢的东西
and many Java API but when you didn't
和许多Java API，但是当您没有
use a value you just use the void upper
使用一个值就可以使用void upper
upper case void which worked a bit weird
大写的void有点奇怪
so we have not used and we have done
所以我们没有用，我们已经做了
type again same thing doesn't carry any
再次输入相同的东西不带任何东西
meaning our van and being easier to read
意味着我们的货车，更易于阅读
so if you get a done value the stream
因此，如果您获得了完成的价值，那么信息流
has completed and a big difference from
已经完成，与
other recta streams implementations we
其他Recta流实现
have a lifted representation so that
具有提升的代表性
means by this time you have a source by
意味着到这个时候你有一个来源
a flow to think it hasn't run yet and
认为它还没有运行的流程
only runs when you run it or how we call
仅在您运行它或我们如何调用时运行
it materialized which allows us to do
它实现了，这使我们能够做到
some interesting either merging of
一些有趣的合并
multiple stages into a single stage and
将多个阶段合并为一个阶段
having this more configurable than not
具有更多的可配置性
and not lifted implementations so here's
并没有取消实施，所以这里是
an example of getting this materialized
一个实例化的例子
value out the sink head is basically a
值从沉头基本上是一个
sink that materializes a completion
实现完成的接收器
stage thank you you can see ok so rerun
阶段谢谢你可以看到确定，所以重新运行
with this sink and it gives us back this
有了这个水槽，它给了我们这个
completion stage which is what I talked
我所说的完成阶段
about this integration with non
关于这种与非
streaming world is pretty important and
流媒体世界非常重要，
and here's something that we programmed
这是我们编程的东西
this way other ways to do that would be
这样其他方式可以做到
more side effecting on the side setting
侧面设置有更多副作用
something we thought that's a bit more
我们认为还有一点
clear this you've seen already we have
清除您已经看到的内容
source flow sink but you can have
源流汇，但您可以拥有
arbitrary many ports if you want ok so
任意多个端口，如果您希望这样
that's I think the last talk about akka
那是我认为关于阿卡的最后一句话
streams the door I just wanted to
流我刚想去的门
explain the building blocks we have so
解释我们拥有的基本要素
you think about into it in terms of
您从以下方面考虑
sinks and flows and sources because the
下沉，流动和来源，因为
entire future of reactive streams and
反应流的整个未来
travel to a concurrent flow is in
进入并发流程
providing building blocks ok so if if
提供积木可以，如果
you have these building blocks and you
你有这些积木，你
know that you're not locked into a
知道你没有被锁定
single implementation because they all
单一实施，因为它们都
inter up you can start thinking about
内部，你可以开始考虑
really picking and choosing parts of
真正挑选和选择
your streaming pipeline
您的流媒体管道
from whatever library is out here and
从这里的任何图书馆
most of them are slowly converting onto
他们中的大多数正在慢慢转化为
these types so we have a nice growing
这些类型，所以我们有一个很好的成长
ecosystem and we can nicely encapsulate
生态系统，我们可以很好地封装
them so for example if you have to
他们，例如，如果您必须
explain bees yeah for example like that
像这样解释蜜蜂是的
you can have some kind of flow with just
你可以拥有某种流动
processors and acts things from Kafka
卡夫卡处理器和行为
and that's maybe from a database you
那也许是从你的数据库
don't really care it's a blue thing and
不在乎这是一件蓝色的事，
on the left hand side that's your logic
在左手边这就是你的逻辑
would be an application our current
将是我们目前的应用
terminology a flow flow terminology
术语流术语
that's a processor one thing in one
这是处理器合而为一的事情
thing out and you can easily replace but
东西出来，你可以轻松地替换，但是
for example this is slightly
例如，这有点
mind-bending once you see it just in
一旦看到它就可以弯曲
normal daily code on a picture I don't
我没有的正常日常代码
think it's so mind-bending so I keep
认为它是如此弯曲，所以我继续
showing in this picture you can replace
如图所示，您可以更换
a function with kind of a conceptual
具有某种概念的功能
functional flow with independent sources
具有独立来源的功能流程
and sinks and that's actually very very
和下沉，实际上是非常非常
interesting both for testing or for
有趣的测试或
example you're injecting some test data
例如您要注入一些测试数据
with your source but the sink side is
与您的来源，但接收器的一面是
still your actual logic and instead of
仍然是您的实际逻辑，而不是
emitting data from your actual logic you
从您的实际逻辑中发出数据
emit it into some assertion collector
将其发送到一些断言收集器
and then with assertion collector you
然后使用断言收集器
just plug it a bit differently together
只是把它插在一起有点不同
and you have this nice power of
而且您拥有强大的力量
composability without having to change
可组合性，无需更改
your actual logic and it's all screaming
你的实际逻辑，这一切都在尖叫
still because we have this abstraction
仍然是因为我们有这种抽象
that allows us to do it so now if we
如果我们现在可以这样做的话
talk about building blocks this is the
谈论积木这是
moment I want to talk about our Parker
现在我想谈谈我们的帕克
project which i think is the important
我认为很重要的项目
bit because I talked about ok library
有点，因为我谈论好的图书馆
interrupts and that's nice
打断，那很好
certainly if you can kind of be assured
当然，如果您可以放心
that you're not gonna be locked into a
你不会被锁在一个
course praying or whatever or you're
当然祈祷或其他任何事情
specifically with are polka you can't
特别是波尔卡，你不能
just use whatever connector that's all
只需使用所有的连接器
streaming connectors including some IBM
流连接器，包括一些IBM
technology
技术
we partnered up servers sometimes or
我们有时与服务器合作或
some I forgot the names of it we haven't
一些我忘记了我们没有的名字
as free compatible API which was
作为免费的兼容API，
actually very funny to work with because
实际上很有趣，因为
we thought we will have to write a
我们认为我们将不得不写一个
specific endpoint to verse IBM as like
像IBM这样的特定端点
as free like API but turned out they
像API一样免费，但事实证明它们
were very compliant with as free API of
非常符合作为的免费API
Amazon so actually we just reused and
亚马逊，所以实际上我们只是重复使用了
shaped up a bit file as free connector
将一个位文件塑造为免费连接器
to be also able to work with our API and
也可以使用我们的API和
that's interesting because you don't
那很有趣，因为你不
have to care as user you just look at
您只需要关注用户
your list okay does alpaca have my
您的清单好吗，羊驼有我的
favorite technology you use the thing
您使用事物最喜欢的技术
and it's a streaming connector to
这是一个流连接器
whatever your favorite technology you
不管你喜欢什么技术
have fair and if you don't then building
公平，如果你不这样做，
it is pretty easy and you can build it
这很简单，您可以构建它
using whatever technology you want you
使用您想要的任何技术
can use our car screams which I would
可以使用我们的汽车尖叫声
highly recommend but you can use
强烈推荐，但您可以使用
anything else as long as it passes well
只要一切顺利就可以
TCK it's a fully streaming and safe
TCK是完全流式传输且安全的
thing that fits into this ecosystem so
适合这个生态系统的东西
instead of being super competitive and
而不是超级竞争
like being very aggressive about yeah we
喜欢对我们非常激进
have a connector for this we have a
为此有一个连接器
connector for that we kind of invested
我们投资的连接器
in a more helpful environment where if
在更有用的环境中，如果
anyone produces a driver like MongoDB to
任何人都会产生像MongoDB这样的驱动程序来
the erect extremes driver everybody can
直立的极端，每个人都可以
use it directly and how does this grow
直接使用它以及它如何增长
if it was among a few months ago just a
如果是在几个月前
number of connectors where some of them
其中一些连接器的数量
we implemented some of them just people
我们实施了其中的一些人
in the community implemented and this is
在社区实施，这是
today and it doesn't even quite fit so I
今天甚至还不太合适，所以我
had to make the text quite smaller so we
必须使文本变小，所以我们
have a lot of things including lambda as
有很多东西，包括lambda
3sn is SQS so a lot of amazon stuff some
3sn是SQS，所以很多亚马逊东西
google api switch are equivalent to
google api开关等效于
vendors and things and here's an
供应商和东西，这是一个
interesting bit is okay if you kind of
如果您喜欢的话，有趣的一点还可以
abstract the way your use of client
抽象您使用客户端的方式
library of specific cloud I don't know
我不知道的特定云库
let's say this messaging API then you
假设这个消息传递API然后
can more easily swap it out if you want
如果需要，可以更轻松地将其换出
so again we're kind of helping you to be
再次，我们很乐意帮助您成为
more flexible and picking whichever
更灵活，可以选择
cloud you want because okay this month
你想要的云，因为这个月还好
here we got a good price next month oh
下个月我们在这里卖个好价钱哦
we did a price reduction let's use ice
我们降价了，让我们用冰
API so and again with always Express the
API总是与Express一起
sources and sinks and flows and you can
源，汇和流，您可以
always if you have a sink you can always
如果有水槽，总是可以
get a subscriber from it if you have a
从中获得订阅者（如果您有）
source you can always get a publisher
来源，您总是可以得到出版商
from it
从中
so again complete and drop so let's look
再次完成并放下，让我们来看一下
at an example how we would you actually
在一个例子中，我们将如何实际
are we envision building streaming apps
我们是否设想构建流媒体应用程序
or more integration labs because when
或更多集成实验室，因为
people say streaming apps it's also a
人们说流媒体应用程序也是
bit confusing because sometimes they
有点令人困惑，因为有时他们
mean the data heavy analytics machine
意味着数据密集型分析机
learning heavy pipelines which usually
学习繁重的管道，通常
spark or or fling technologies back that
激发或激发技术
were they own the entire pipeline and
他们是否拥有整个管道？
they start the stream and they run with
他们开始流，他们与
stream directive streams and flow here
流指令流和流在这里
is really more about small jobs that
真的更多是关于小型工作的
have to be done and it would be nice if
必须做的，这将是很好，如果
they were streaming and we don't have to
他们正在流式传输，我们不必
have 50 nodes to do it we can do it in a
有50个节点可以做到
single node because that's actually
单节点，因为实际上
sometimes faster and now if you've seen
有时更快，现在，如果您已经看到
there were a few examples of people kind
有一些善良的例子
of comparing setting and wrapping with
比较设置和包装
Hadoop in a problem setting and wrapping
Hadoop中的问题设置和包装
would be some simpler and faster but
会更简单更快
yeah we want to be enterprise-d and used
是的，我们希望成为企业级产品并使用
for big things right maybe you don't
做大事吧，也许你不会
need to use with big things so it's more
需要使用大物件，所以更多
sidenote so how would I build a thing
旁注，那么我将如何建造一个东西
with our poker you just pick okay I want
用我们的扑克，你只要选择我想要的
to I want to use - kafra streaming is
我想使用-kafra流式传输是
that include the dependency here I'm
在这里包括依赖
gonna include okay HTTP just because I
会包括好的HTTP只是因为我
like it then basically you pick what
喜欢它，然后基本上你选择什么
source you want right so we kind of
您想要正确的来源，所以我们有点
explained by the name what kind of
用名字解释什么样的
semantics we have and at most source and
我们拥有的语义以及最多的来源和
committable source and we give you
可提交的源代码，我们给您
slightly different types here are I
我这里的类型略有不同
lined them a bit and you can see okay
排一下他们，你可以看到
you get a consumer record or
您会获得消费者记录或
committable message so if a cognitive
可提交的消息，因此，如果认知
message one you're in charge of hitting
留言一个你负责打
commit on each message and when we do a
提交每条消息，当我们做一个
cumulative to a given offset commit and
累积到给定的偏移量提交和
as I said we have this outside control
正如我所说的，我们有这种外部控制
parameter that you can control this
您可以控制的参数
running stream and ever get metrics out
运行流并获得指标
of it or stop it or pause it things like
它或停止它或暂停它之类的东西
that so you picked one of those and then
这样，您选择了其中一个，然后
you basically just need to and they
您基本上只需要，他们
screwed up the slide a bit but basically
稍微弄乱了幻灯片，但基本上
we need to connect some source to
我们需要将一些源连接到
something basically as simple as that
基本上就这么简单
and resonant entire a streaming HTTP F
并谐振整个流HTTP F
out of Kafka you just pick a source
从卡夫卡出来，你只是选择一个来源
because ink runs HTTP server you're done
因为墨水可以运行HTTP服务器
so this is a bit underwhelming to show
所以这有点让人难以理解
perhaps because okay three lines some
也许是因为三行好
magic the thing is it's actually not
魔术，实际上不是
magic it's very boring tech it just
魔术，这是非常无聊的技术
connects because we have the same types
连接，因为我们有相同的类型
everywhere and it just works because his
到处都是，因为他的
under under under under covers agreement
低于低于低于涵盖
between these different libraries but
这些不同的库之间，但
once you can realize that this is how I
一旦你意识到这就是我的方式
can plug stuff together I think it's
可以把东西塞在一起，我认为是
pretty well call it profit and then you
很好，称之为利润，然后你
just change for sources or syncs you can
只需更改来源或同步即可
be an FTP thing can be whatever you want
成为FTP东西可以随心所欲
for just works training and like I said
只是为了工作训练，就像我说的
this is our Parker community again you I
这又是我们的帕克社区
would like you to use it without code
希望您不带代码使用它
but you can use it before that whatever
但您可以在此之前使用它
you want so pretty inclusive and last
你想要如此包容而持久
thing that's something people don't
人们不喜欢的东西
often think about is that an HTTP server
经常想到的是一个HTTP服务器
can also be made streaming how do we do
也可以制作流媒体我们该怎么办
that we do that by expressing the HTTP
我们通过表达HTTP来做到这一点
server and for HTTP entity again as
服务器和HTTP实体再次作为
reactive streams WebSockets as well wait
反应性流WebSockets以及等待
a moment because
片刻因为
taking picture so the interesting bit
拍照很有趣
here is this precise more precisely
这是更精确的
models HTTP to van a server as a phone
建模HTTP以将服务器用作电话
when the server is a function because a
当服务器是一个功能，因为
server as a function kind of implies one
服务器作为一种功能隐含着
thing in one thing out
一物一物
hey flow a processor can have one thing
嘿，处理器可以拥有一件事
in many things out so that models the
在很多事情上，以便建模
server approach of HTTP to or you get
HTTP的服务器方法或您得到
one request and you start pushing the
一个请求，您就开始推动
assets right away so nice side effect
资产马上就这么好副作用
and then again buffers all the way down
然后一直缓冲下去
I as I said and we basically propagate
正如我所说，我们基本上会传播
both pushing of the data that's all
都推送所有数据
reactive streams all the way to the TCP
反应性流一直到TCP
implementation we have and over active
我们已经实施并且过度活跃
libraries as well and we propagate for
图书馆，我们传播
back pressure or the way from the OS
背压或操作系统的方式
from the windowing mechanism of TCP into
从TCP的窗口机制
actually pulling more tweets or not
实际上是否拉更多推文
literally if TCP is getting back
从字面上看是否TCP正在恢复
pressure because someone is in a tunnel
压力，因为有人在隧道里
and is not receiving data we will stop
并且没有收到数据，我们将停止
pulling the string so it's also from
拉线，所以它也是从
that site pretty interesting again how
该网站再次很有趣
much core code is that source repeat a
许多核心代码是源重复
tweet okay that's okay HTTP specifics
没关系，HTTP细节还可以
but that's basically path tweets and
但这基本上是路径推文，
when you complete it with these tweets
当您通过这些推文完成它时
as Jason some boilerplate but not too
作为杰森一些样板，但不是太
bad
坏
you start for server you have a fully
您开始为服务器，您已经完全
streaming HTTP server that we're stopped
我们停止的流HTTP服务器
streaming the data to the client and
流数据到客户端
basically emitting this new tweet load
基本上会发出这种新的推文负载
right this could be a heavy operation
对，这可能是一个繁重的操作
this could be pulling from a database or
这可能是从数据库中提取的，或者
something so it would stop invoking
东西，所以它将停止调用
first thing if there would be no demand
如果没有需求，第一件事
on the user's phone so pretty cool the
在用户的手机上非常酷
same thing in Scala as I said way over
跟我说的一样，在Scala中也是一样
to API it's a pretty similar a bit more
与API相当相似
concise but not too much so you can
简洁但不要太多，因此您可以
stick to whichever you want and adoption
坚持任何您想要和采用的
right so and so is this thing actually
对，这东西实际上
getting adoption from the big guys
从大人物那里领养
Amazon's of
亚马逊的
as decay announced there will be an
随着衰变的宣布，将会有一个
basically exposing all of our libraries
基本上公开我们所有的图书馆
with reactive streams and that again
与反应性流，并再次
means they will be compatible with JDK
意味着它们将与JDK兼容
types we already have a very exciting
类型，我们已经有一个非常令人兴奋的
project in JDK 10 which is for a
JDK 10中的项目
synchronous asynchronous JDBC which is
同步异步JDBC是
finally coming it seems and of course
似乎终于来了，当然
they'll be using those executive types
他们将使用那些执行类型
so that's a flow subscription to give
所以这是一个流订阅
you streaming data out and into the
您将数据流式传输到
database so this is something I'm very
数据库，这是我非常喜欢的东西
excited about because it was kind of
感到兴奋，因为它有点
long requested by many people and also I
长期以来，很多人都要求我
was a bit afraid because we wanted to
有点害怕，因为我们想
ship it in 9 which mean which would have
将其运送到9，这意味着
meant they wouldn't have time to adopt
意味着他们没有时间收养
reactive streams thing and it would be a
反应流的东西，这将是
streaming thing but not reactive streams
流的东西，而不是反应流
my waiting from JDK 10 was actually a
我在JDK 10中的等待实际上是
super good timing
超级好时机
vra so they can use a kind of ready
véra，所以他们可以使用一种现成的
ecosystem and just jump right in it's
生态系统，就在其中
more of a slide about akka and how how
更多关于akka的幻灯片以及如何
kind of complexity and power interact
那种复杂性和权力互动
within one another basically what I want
彼此之间基本上是我想要的
to say is just don't use threads and
就是不使用线程而已
locks directly okay if you think about
如果您考虑一下，直接锁定就可以了
oh I have this concurrency problem and
哦，我有这个并发问题，
and you start using the low-level
然后您开始使用低级
primitives okay could be a fun project
原语好吧可能是一个有趣的项目
for evenings but don't put that in
晚上，但不要把它放进去
production because when we see just
生产，因为当我们看到
wrong things and verse better tools out
错误的事情和更好的工具
for me it's dreaming or act or so
对我来说，这是在做梦或行动
anything so yeah mmm
嗯嗯
we obviously have monitoring focus the
我们显然有监控重点
monitoring would be our custom specific
监控将是我们自定义的
not flow specifically but it's being
没有具体流动，但它正在
ready to adopt and prod absolutely
准备绝对采用和生产
because over the last three years we've
因为在过去三年中
seen big adoption of reactive streams we
看到被动流的大量采用
know it's picking up we've seen the big
知道它正在回升，我们已经看到了
players adopted so it's only a matter of
玩家采用了，所以这只是一个问题
time of people hopping onto JDK 9 and
人们跳上JDK 9和
being happy in jail we have a conference
在监狱里开心我们开会
but focused more on the reactive side of
但更多地侧重于反应的方面
things so it's not a scarlet conference
事情，所以这不是一个猩红色的会议
sometimes people ask me that being you
有时候人们问我是你
know kind of related to ask our
知道某种相关的问我们
ecosystem it's a specifically reactive
生态系统是一种特别的反应
architecture conference it's in two
建筑会议分为两个部分
weeks from now if you want to discount
如果要打折，请从现在起数周
them you know and yeah that's all I have
他们你知道，是的，我所拥有的
and if you have any questions I'm not
如果您有任何疑问，我不会
sure how we're on time I think we're
确定我们如何准时我认为我们
over time but you can grab me I have
随着时间的流逝，但是你可以抓住我
some stickers or would be happy to
一些贴纸或乐于
discuss or answer any questions so
讨论或回答任何问题
thanks a lot
非常感谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]